(Sheldon:)Have you developed any
of the following symptoms?
(Sheldon:)A growing nose or perhaps a warm sensation
in the trouser region?
(Sheldon:)Also known as full-blown
Liar, Liar, Pants on Fire.
(Amy:)All right, all right.
But I really was sick at the beginning.
(Amy:)It's just been so nice
having you take care of me.
(Sheldon:)It hurts that you would lie to me, Amy.
(Sheldon:)I thought our relationship
was based on trust...
(Sheldon:)...and a mutual admiration
that skews in my favor.
(Amy:)I feel terrible I did this.
(Sheldon:)It pains me to say it,
but I think some form of penalty is in order...
...so as to discourage this type of behavior
in the future.
(Amy:)I suppose that's fair. What do you suggest?
(Sheldon:)In a perfect world, I'd lock you in a stockade
in the public square.
And that probably requires a permit.
(Amy:)I could not be allowed to go to the opening
of the next Star Trek movie.